[Music]
we are super thrilled and excited to win
the award for the first time
we thank cnbc tv 18 for
recognizing the agility and resilience
which gsk pharma has displayed in a very
difficult pandemic year in 2021 first
and foremost uh
the majority of the risk culture and how
it is embedded across all levels in the
organization is a clear standout for us
the second is of course the ability to
use data and analytics
in the way we make our decisions robust
embedded in risk
culture and third and most importantly
we are in the business of serving our
patients so making sure that in the most
difficult challenging circumstances uh
during the pandemic we ensured
an uninterrupted supply of critical
medicines which were needed uh to serve
millions of patients across the country
ici's hair lombard and cnbc tv 18
present india risk management awards
honoring the new age risk management
practitioners